chronoblade.com 2018-10-23

# Privacy Policy - Chrono BladeChrono Blade

This Privacy Policy explains our practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of information that we receive when you visit our Site and use our Service. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any third party websites, services or applications, including any websites, services and applications that you may access through our Service. Unless we define a term in this Privacy Policy, all capitalized words used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms of Service.

###### HOW DO WE COLLECT AND USE INFORMATION?

Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve our Service, to administer your use of the Service (and, if you have registered an account with us, administer your account), and to enable you to enjoy and easily navigate our Service.

Account Information. When you create an account, we will collect certain information that can be used to identify you, such as your name and email address (“PII”). We may also collect certain information that is not PII because it cannot be used by itself to identify you, such as your gender, birth date or age, and zip code. If you choose to create an account using a Social Networking Service, you will provide us with your username (or user ID) so that your identity can be authenticated by the Social Networking Service account. When the authentication is complete, we’ll be able to link your account with the Social  
Networking Service account and access certain PII, such as your name and email address, and other information that your privacy settings on the Social Networking Service account permit us to access.

Information Collected Using Cookies. We collect certain information through the use of “cookies,” which are small text files that are saved by your browser when you access our Service. We may use both  
session cookies and persistent cookies to identify that you’ve logged in to the Service and to tell us how and when you interact with our Service. We may also use cookies to monitor aggregate usage and web  
traffic routing on our Service and to customize and improve our Service. Unlike persistent cookies, session cookies are deleted when you log off from the Service and close your browser. Although most  
browsers automatically accept cookies, you can change your browser options to stop automatically accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting cookies. Please note, however, that if you don’t  
accept cookies, you may not be able to access all portions of the Service. Some third party services providers that we engage (including third party advertisers) may also place their own cookies on your  
browser. Note that this Privacy Policy covers only our use of cookies and does not include use of cookies by such third parties.

Information Related to Use of the Service . Our servers automatically record certain information about how a person uses our Service (we refer to this information as “Log Data”), including both account  
holders and non-account holders (either, a “User”). Log Data may include information such as a User’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, operating system, the web page that a User was visiting  
before accessing our Service, the pages or features of our Service to which a User browsed and the time spent on those pages or features, search terms, the links on our Service that a User clicked on and other statistics. We use this information to administer the Service and we analyze (and may engage third parties to analyze) this information to improve and enhance the Service by expanding their features and functionality and tailoring them to our Users’ needs and preferences. We generally use IP addresses to fight spam, malware and identity theft. We also use the IP Address to generate aggregate, non-identifying information about how our Service is used.

Location Information. In some cases, we collect and store information about where you are located, such as by converting your IP address into a rough geolocation. We may use location information to improve and personalize our Service for you.

###### WHAT INFORMATION DO WE SHARE WITH THIRD PARTIES?

We will not share any PII that we have collected from you except as described below:  
Information Shared with Our Service Providers. We may engage third party service providers to work with us to administer and provide the Service. These third party services providers have access to your  
information only to the extent necessary and for the purpose of performing services on our behalf.

Information Shared with Third Parties. We may share aggregated information and non-identifying information with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling and other similar purposes.

Information We Disclose With Your Consent or at Your Request. We will share your PII with third party sites or platforms, such as social networking sites, if you have expressly requested that we do so.

Information Disclosed in Connection with Business Transactions. Information that we collect from our users is considered to be a business asset and if we are acquired as a result of a transaction such as a  
merger, acquisition or asset sale, or if we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, your information would be transferred to a third party as a business asset in connection with such a transaction.

Information Disclosed for Our Protection and the Protection of Others. We may disclose information about you to government or law enforcement officials or to private parties as we, in our reasonable discretion, believe it is necessary: (i) to satisfy or comply with any applicable law, regulation or legal process or to respond to lawful requests, including subpoenas, warrants or court orders; (ii) to protect our property, rights and safety and the rights, property and safety of third parties or the public in general; and (iii) to prevent or stop activity we consider to be illegal or unethical.

###### **THE SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION**

We take reasonable measures to protect the information that we collect from or about you from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Please be aware, however, that no method of transmitting  
information over the Internet or storing information is completely secure and we cannot guarantee the absolute security of any information.

###### LINKS TO OTHER SITES

Our Service may contain links to other websites and services. Any information that you provide on or to a third party website or service is provided directly to the owner of the website or service and is subject to that party’s privacy policy. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to such websites or services and we’re not responsible for the content, privacy or security practices and policies of those websites or services. To protect your information, we recommend that you carefully review the privacy policies of other websites and services that you access.

###### MODIFYING YOUR INFORMATION

You can access and modify your personal information through your account. If you want us to delete any of your personal information and/or your account, please contact us at powerrangers@nway.com with your request. We’ll take steps to delete your information as soon as is practicable, but some information may remain in archived/backup copies for our records or as otherwise required by law.

###### INTERNATIONAL USERS

Your information may be transferred to, and maintained on, computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you’re located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, we may transfer your information to the United States and process it there (or any other country in which we operate).

###### OUR POLICY TOWARD CHILDREN

Our Service is not directed to children under 13 and we do not knowingly collect PII from children under 13. If we learn that we have collected PII of someone under 13 we will take steps to delete such  
information from our files as soon as possible.

###### CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY

Any information that we collect is subject to the privacy policy in effect at the time such information is collected. We may, however, modify and revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make any  
material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you of such changes by posting them on the Service or by sending you an email or other notification, and we will indicate when such changes will become effective.

###### QUESTIONS?

Please contact us if you have any questions about our Privacy Policy.
